Register of the Ivan D. London papers
Hoover Institution Archives
- Printed Matter, 1949-1971
  - Soobshcheniia (Mitteilungen), Komitet po zashchite Russkoi Pravoslavnoi Tserkvi v Zapadnoi Germanii ot kommunizma, No. 4, 1963 (Box-folder 87: 12)
  - "Tetrad' "Vol'noi Mysli," Nos. 2 and 3, 1964 (Box-folder 87: 13)
  - Vedomosti Soveta Vosstanovleniia Rossiiskogo Gosudarstva (Information Bulletin of the Council of the Re-Establishment of the Russian State), Nos. 1-2, 1953 (Box-folder 87: 14)
  - U.S. News & World Report, 1956 November 2 and 1957 July 12 (Box-folder 87: 15)
  - World Association for Public Opinion Research (WAPOR), directory, 1965-1966 (Box-folder 87: 16)
- Oversize Material, 1951-1985
  Serial issues arranged alphabetically by title.
  - The American Spectator, Nos. 8 (1978), 1 (1979), 2 (1980), 1 and 4 (1981), 7-8 (1982), 2 and 11 (1984), June 1985, 1978-1985 (Box-folder 90: 1)
  - Golos Rossii, Vestnik russkoi natsional'no-patrioticheskoi pravoslavno-khristianskoi mysli, Munich, Nos. 17, 19-23 (1956), 1-5 (1957), 1956-1957 (Box-folder 90: 2)
  - Izvestia, Nos. 82, 142, 144, and 148, 1957 (Box-folder 90: 3)
  - Komsomol'skaia Pravda, Nos. 2 and 79, 1957 (Box-folder 90: 4)
  - Monthly Review, Vol. 7, 1982 (Box-folder 90: 5)
  - Nabat, Munich, Nos. 43 (1953), 44-51(1954), 56 (1956), 1953-1956 (Box-folder 90: 6)
  - The New York Times Magazine, section 6, 1951 November 21 and 1970 January 4 (Box-folder 90: 7)
  - Posev, No. 15, 1957 (Box-folder 90: 8)
  - Pravda, No. 93, 1957 (Box-folder 90: 9)
  - Smena, No. 2, 1967 (Box-folder 90: 10)
  - Trud, Nos. 79, 147, and 150, 1957 (Box-folder 90: 11)
  - Za vozvrashchenie na Rodinu, izdanie komiteta "Za vozvrashchenie na Rodinu," Berlin, Nos. 21, 47, and 48, 1957 (Box-folder 90: 12)